Finding Aid for Provost and Executive Vice-President for Academic Affairs (University of Michigan) Supplemental Files, 1952-[ongoing]
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Supplemental Files
  - Searches 1983-2001
    - Financial Aid, Director of the Office of
      - 1996-1997 (Pamela Fowler)
        - Background Information on Financial Aid Office (Box 27)
        - Candidates (Box 27)
        - Correspondence (Box 27)
        - Evaluation of Candidates (Box 27)
        - Final Report to the Provost (Box 27)
        - Forms and Form Letters (Box 27)
        - Interview Questions (Box 27)
        - Position Description and Selection Criteria (Box 27)
        - Questions for Referees (Box 27)
        - Search Committee Agendas and Minutes (Box 27)
        - Search Committee Membership (Box 27)
        - Finalist Files, 4 folders (Box 27)
    - Graduate Studies, Horace H. Rackham School of
      - 1984-1985 (John D'Arms)
        - Advertisement (Box 27)
        - Background Information on Rackham (Box 27)
        - Correspondence (Box 27)
        - Final Report to the Provost (Box 27)
        - Position Description and Selection Criteria (Box 27)
        - Provost's Report to the Regents (Box 27)
        - Search Committee Agendas and Minutes (Box 28)
        - Search Committee Membership (Box 28)
        - Finalist Files, 4 folders (Box 28)
        - 1994-1995 (Nancy Cantor) (Box 28)
        - Advertisement (Box 28)
        - Background Information on Rackham (Box 28)
        - Briefing Book for the Candidates (Box 28)
        - Candidates (Box 28)
        - Correspondence (Box 28)
        - Evaluation of Candidates (Box 28)
        - Final Report to the Provost (Box 28)
        - Forms and Form Letters (Box 28)
        - Interview Questions (Box 28)
        - Position Description and Selection Criteria (Box 28)
        - Press (Box 28)
        - Provost's Report to the Regents (Box 28)
        - Search Committee Agendas and Minutes (Box 28)
        - Search Committee Membership (Box 28)
        - Finalist Files, 4 folders (Box 28)
      - 1997-1998 (Earl Lewis)
        - Advertisement (Box 28)
        - Background (Box 28)
        - Candidates (Box 28)
        - Correspondence (Box 28)
        - Final Report to the Provost (Box 28)
        - Forms and Form Letters (Box 28)
        - Interview Questions (Box 28)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 28)
        - Position Description and Selection Criteria (Box 28)
        - Provost's Report to the Regents (Box 28)
        - Search Committee Agendas and Minutes (Box 28)
        - Search Committee Membership (Box 28)
        - Timeline (Box 28)
        - Finalist Files, 4 folders (Box 28)
    - Human Resources and Affirmative Action, Executive Director
      - 1992-1993 (Jackie McClain)
        - Advertisement (Box 28)
        - Candidates (Box 28)
        - Interview Questions (Box 28)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 28)
        - Position Description and Summary of Qualifications (Box 28)
        - Provost's Report to the Regents (Box 28)
        - Search Committee Agendas and Minutes (Box 28)
        - Search Committee Membership (Box 28)
        - Search Consultants (Box 28)
        - Finalist Files, 6 folders (Box 28)
      - 1999-2000 (Barbara Butterfield) [Associate Vice President]
        - Advertisement (Box 28)
        - Candidates (Box 28)
        - Correspondence (Box 28)
        - Interview Questions (Box 28)
        - Position Description and Selection Criteria (Box 28)
        - Search Committee Agendas and Minutes (Box 28)
        - Search Committee Membership (Box 28)
        - Search Consultants (Box 28)
        - Timeline (Box 28)
        - Finalist Files, 3 folders (Box 28)
    - Information, School of
      - 1984-1985 (Robert Warner) (School of Library Science) (Box 29)
      - 1991-1992 (Dan Atkins) (School of Information and Library Studies)
        [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2022 ]
        - Advertisement (Box 29)
        - Background Information on School (Box 29)
        - Candidates (Box 29)
        - Correspondence (Box 29)
        - E-mails (Box 29)
        - Final Report to the Provost (Box 29)
        - Forms and Form Letters (Box 29)
        - Notes (Box 29)
        - Position Description and Selection Criteria (Box 29)
        - Press (Box 29)
        - Provost's Poll of the Faculty on Issues Related to SILS (Box 29)
        - Provost's Report of the Regents (Box 29)
        - Search Committee Agendas and Minutes (Box 29)
        - Search Committee Membership (Box 29)
        - Timeline (Box 29)
        - Finalist Files, 5 folders (Box 29)
      - 1998-1999 (John King)
        - Advertisement (Box 29)
        - Background Information on the School of Information (Box 29)
        - Candidates (Box 29)
        - E-mails (Box 29)
        - Forms and Form Letters (Box 29)
        - Interview Questions (Box 29)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 29)
        - Position Description and Selection Criteria (Box 29)
        - Search Committee Agendas and Minutes (Box 29)
        - Search Committee Membership (Box 29)
        - Search Consultants (Box 29)
        - Timeline (Box 29)
        - Finalist Files, 5 folders (Box 29)
    - Information Technology Division, Director of
      - 1995-1996 (Jose-Marie Griffiths)
        - Candidates (Box 29)
        - Correspondence (Box 29)
        - Forms and Form Letters (Box 29)
        - Interview Questions (Box 29)
        - Position Description and Selection Criteria (Box 29)
        - Search Committee Agendas and Minutes (Box 29)
        - Search Committee Membership (Box 29)
        - Search Consultants (Box 29)
        - Finalist Files, 4 folders (Box 29)
    - Institute for Foreign Area and International Studies
      - 1992-1993 (Box 29)
    - Kinesiology, Director of the Division of
      - 1998 (Beverly Ulrich)
        - Advertisement (Box 29)
        - Position Description and Selection Criteria (Box 29)
        - Search Committee Membership (Box 29)
        - Finalist Files, 2 folders (Box 30)
    - Law School
      - 1977-1978 (Terrance Sandalow) (Box 30)
      - 1986-1987 (Lee Bollinger) (Box 30)
        [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2017 ]
      - 1993-1994 (Jeffrey Lehman)
        [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2024 ]
        - Advertisement (Box 30)
        - Candidates (Box 30)
        - Correspondence (Box 30)
        - Position Description and Selection Criteria (Box 30)
        - Provost's Report to the Regents (Box 30)
        - Report to the Provost (Box 30)
        - Search Committee Agendas and Minutes (Box 30)
        - Search Committee Membership (Box 30)
        - Finalist Files, 3 folders (Box 30)
    - Library, University
      - 1977-1978 (Richard M. Dougherty) (Box 30)
      - 1989-1990 (Don Riggs)
        - Advertisement (Box 30)
        - Background Information on the University Library (Box 30)
        - Candidates (Box 30)
        - E-mail and Correspondence (Box 30)
        - Final Report to the Provost (Box 30)
        - Forms and Form Letters (Box 30)
        - Position Description and Selection Criteria (Box 30)
        - Provost's Poll of the Faculty and Staff on Issues for the University Library (Box 30)
        - Search Committee Agendas and Minutes (Box 30)
        - Search Committee Membership (Box 30)
        - Search Consultants (Box 30)
        - Finalist Files, 4 folders (Box 30)
      - 1996-1997 (Not filled)
        - Advertisement (Box 30)
        - Background Information on the University Library and School of Information, 2 folders (Box 30)
        - Candidates (Box 30)
        - Correspondence (Box 30)
        - E-mail (Box 30)
        - Final Report to the Provost (Box 30)
        - Forms and Form Letters (Box 30)
        - Interview Questions (Box 30)
        - Position Description and Selection Criteria (Box 30)
        - Provost's Poll of the Faculty and Staff on Issues for the University Library (Box 30)
        - Questions for References (Box 30)
        - Research Materials (Box 30)
        - Search Committee Agendas and Minutes (Box 30)
        - Search Committee Membership (Box 30)
        - Search Consultants (Box 30)
        - Timeline (Box 30)
        - Finalist Files, 3 folders (Box 31)
      - 1998 (Bill Gosling)
        - Gosling, Bill (Box 31)
    - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of
      - 1980-1981 (Peter Steiner) (Box 31)
      - 1988-1989 (Edie Goldenberg)
        - Advertisement (Box 31)
        - Background Information on the College of LS&A, 2 folders (Box 31)
        - Candidate Evaluations (Box 31)
        - Candidates (Box 31)
        - Correspondence (Box 31)
        - Final Report to the Provost (Box 31)
        - Forms and Form Letters (Box 31)
        - Interview Questions (Box 31)
        - Notes (Box 31)
        - Position Description and Selection Criteria (Box 31)
        - Press (Box 31)
        - Provost's Report to the Regents (Box 31)
        - Search Committee Agendas and Minutes (Box 31)
        - Search Committee Chair's Notes (Box 31)
        - Search Committee Membership (Box 31)
        - Search Consultants (Box 31)
        - Student Input (Box 31)
        - Timeline (Box 31)
        - Vice President for Academic Affairs Poll of Faculty on Issues for LS&A and Comments to Committee, 2 folders (Box 31)
        - Finalist Files, 4 folders (Box 31)
      - 1998-1999 (Shirley Neuman)
        - Advertisement (Box 31)
        - Background Information on LS&A (Box 31)
        - Candidates (Box 31)
        - Correspondence (Box 31)
        - Final Report to the Provost (Box 31)
        - Forms and Form Letters (Box 31)
        - Interview Questions (Box 31)
        - Position Description and Selection Criteria (Box 31)
        - Provost's Poll of the Faculty on Issues for LS&A (Box 31)
        - Search Committee Agendas and Minutes (Box 31)
        - Search Committee Membership (Box 31)
        - Search Consultants (Box 31)
        - Timeline (Box 31)
        - Finalist Files (folders 1-2 of 6) (Box 31)
        - Finalist Files (folders 3-6 of 6) (Box 32)
    - Media Union (Renamed Duderstadt Center in 2004), Director
      - 1997 (Barbara O'Keefe)
        - Advertisement (Box 32)
        - Background Information on Media Union and North Campus (Box 32)
        - Candidates (Box 32)
        - Correspondence (Box 32)
        - Forms and Form Letters (Box 32)
        - Interview Questions (Box 32)
        - Position Description and Selection Criteria (Box 32)
        - Search Committee Agendas and Minutes (Box 32)
        - Search Committee Membership (Box 32)
        - Search Consultants (Box 32)
        - Timeline (Box 32)
        - Finalist Files, 7 folders (Box 32)
    - Medical School
      - 1982-1985 (Joseph Johnson, November 1982-December 1983 while Medical School administration was reorganized)
        - Advertisement (Box 32)
        - Background Information on the Medical School (Box 32)
        - Candidates (Box 32)
        - Correspondence (Box 32)
        - Interim Dean Peter Ward (Box 32)
        - Notes of Robin Jacoby (Box 32)
        - Position Description and Selection Criteria (Box 32)
        - Provost's Report to the Regents (Box 32)
        - Search Committee Agendas and Minutes (Box 32)
        - Search Committee Membership (Box 32)
        - Search Committee Memoranda (Box 32)
        - Search Consultants (Box 32)
        - Timeline (Box 32)
        - Finalist Files, 6 folders (Box 32)
      - 1990-1991 (Giles Bole)
        - Advertisement (Box 33)
        - Background Information on the Medical School, 2 folders (Box 33)
        - Candidates (Box 33)
        - Correspondence (Box 33)
        - Final Report to the Provost (Box 33)
        - Forms and Form Letters (Box 33)
        - Position Description and Selection Criteria (Box 33)
        - Provost's Report to the Regents (Box 33)
        - Search Committee Agendas and Minutes (Box 33)
        - Search Committee Chair's Notes (Box 33)
        - Search Committee Membership (Box 33)
        - Search Consultants (Box 33)
        - Timeline (Box 33)
        - Finalist Files, 4 folders (Box 33)
      - 1996 (Search abandoned in November 1996 pending selection of new Executive Vice President for Medical Affairs)
        - Advertisement (Box 33)
        - Background Information on the Medical School, 2 folders (Box 33)
        - Candidates (Box 33)
        - Correspondence (Box 33)
        - Final Report to the Provost (Box 33)
        - Forms and Form Letters (Box 33)
        - Position Description and Selection Criteria (Box 33)
        - Press (Box 33)
        - Provost's Poll of the Faculty on Issues for the Medical School (Box 33)
        - Search Committee Agendas and Minutes (Box 33)
        - Search Committee Membership (Box 33)
        - Search Consultants (Box 33)
        - Timeline (Box 33)
    - Music, School of
      - 1978-1979 (Paul Boylan) (Box 33)
      - 1999-2000 (Karen Wolff)
        - Advertisement (Box 33)
        - Affirmative Action Report (Box 33)
        - Background Information on the School of Music, 2 folders (Box 33)
        - Candidates (Box 34)
        - Correspondence (Box 34)
        - Forms and Form Letters (Box 34)
        - Interviews (Box 34)
        - Meetings with Other Deans, Executive Officers and Others (Box 34)
        - Position Description and Selection Criteria (Box 34)
        - Press (Box 34)
        - Provost's Report to the Regents (Box 34)
        - Search Committee Agendas and Minutes (Box 34)
        - Search Committee Membership (Box 34)
        - Search Consultants (Box 34)
        - Timeline (Box 34)
        - Finalist Files, 4 folders (Box 34)
        - Other Candidate files, 35 folders (Box 34)
          [retain until 2007]
    - Natural Resources [and Environment], School of
      - 1990-1991 (Gary Brewer)
        - Advertisement (Box 34)
        - Background on the School of Natural Resources (Box 34)
        - Candidates (Box 34)
        - Correspondence (Box 34)
        - Exit Interviews (Box 34)
        - Forms and Form Letters (Box 34)
        - Position Description and Selection Criteria (Box 34)
        - Provost's Poll of the Faculty on Issues for SNR (Box 34)
        - Provost's Report to the Regents (Box 34)
        - Search Committee Agendas and Minutes (Box 35)
        - Timeline (Box 35)
        - Finalist Files, 7 folders (Box 35)
      - 1995-1996 (Daniel Mazmanian)
        - Advertisement (Box 35)
        - Background Information on SNRE (Box 35)
        - Candidates (Box 35)
        - Correspondence (Box 35)
        - E-Mail, 2 folders (Box 35)
        - Final Report to the Provost (Box 35)
        - Forms and Form Letters (Box 35)
        - Interviews (Box 35)
        - Position Description and Selection Criteria (Box 35)
        - Press (Box 35)
        - Provost's Poll of the Faculty on Issues for SNRE (Box 35)
        - Provost's Report to the Regents (Box 35)
        - Search Committee Agendas and Minutes (Box 35)
        - Search Committee Membership (Box 35)
        - Search Consultants (Box 35)
        - Timeline (Box 35)
        - Finalist Files, 6 folders (Box 35)
      - 2000-2001 (Rosina Bierbaum)
        - Advertisement (Box 35)
        - Background Information on SNRE, 2 folders (Box 35)
        - Candidates (Box 35)
        - Correspondence (Box 35)
        - Feedback by Other UM Deans on SNRE Deanship (Box 35)
        - Final Report to the Provost (Box 35)
        - Forms and Form Letters (Box 35)
        - Interviews (Box 35)
        - Position Description and Selection Criteria (Box 35)
        - Provost's Poll of the Faculty on Issues for SNRE (Box 35)
        - Search Committee Agendas and Minutes (Box 35)
        - Search Committee Membership (Box 36)
        - Search Consultants (Box 36)
        - "Stars" (Box 36)
        - Timeline (Box 36)
        - Finalist Files, 6 folders (Box 36)
        - Other Candidate Files, 36 folders (Box 36)
        - Other Candidate Files, 3 folders (Box 37)
    - Neuroscience Program, Director
      - 1990 (Box 37)
    - Nursing, School of
      - 1992-1993 (Ada Sue Hinshaw)
        - Advertisement (Box 37)
        - Background Information on the School of Nursing (Box 37)
        - Candidates (Box 37)
        - Correspondence (Box 37)
        - E-Mail (Box 37)
        - Final Report to the Provost (Box 37)
        - Forms and Form Letters (Box 37)
        - Interview Questions (Box 37)
        - Position Description and Selection Criteria (Box 37)
        - Provost's Poll of the Faculty on Issues for the School (Box 37)
        - Search Committee Agendas and Minutes (Box 37)
        - Search Committee Membership (Box 37)
        - Timeline (Box 37)
        - Finalist Files, 4 folders (Box 37)
    - Pharmacy, College of
      - 1994-1995 (Not filled)
        - Advertisement (Box 37)
        - Background Information on Pharmacy, 2 folders (Box 37)
        - Candidates (Box 37)
        - Correspondence (Box 37)
        - Forms and Form Letters (Box 37)
        - Interview Questions (Box 37)
        - Position Description and Selection Criteria (Box 37)
        - Search Committee Agendas and Minutes (Box 37)
        - Search Committee Membership (Box 37)
        - Search Consultants (Box 37)
        - Finalist Files, 4 folders (Box 37)
      - 1997-1998 (George Kenyon)
        - Advertisement (Box 37)
        - Background Information on Pharmacy, 2 folders (Box 37)
        - Candidate Evaluations (Box 37)
        - Candidates (Box 37)
        - Correspondence (Box 37)
        - Final Report to the Provost (Box 37)
        - Forms and Form Letters (Box 37)
        - Interview Questions (Box 37)
        - Nomination Solicitation (Box 37)
        - Position Description and Selection Criteria (Box 38)
        - Search Committee Agendas and Minutes (Box 38)
        - Search Committee Membership (Box 38)
        - Search Consultants (Box 38)
        - Timeline (Box 38)
        - Finalist Files, 4 folders (Box 38)
    - President
      - 1995-1996 (Lee Bollinger)
        - Advertisement (Box 38)
        - Ann Arbor News, Detroit Free Press, Detroit News Lawsuit vs. Regents (Box 38)
        - Background Information on the University of Michigan (Box 38)
        - Budget (Box 38)
        - Correspondence (Box 38)
        - Notes (Box 38)
        - Position Description and Selection Criteria (Box 38)
        - Press (Box 38)
        - Regent's Presidential Search Committee (Box 38)
        - Search Advisory Committee Agendas and Minutes (Box 38)
        - Search Advisory Committee Membership (Box 38)
        - Search Committee Nominations--Alumni (Box 38)
        - Search Committee Nominations--Faculty (Box 38)
        - Search Committee Nominations--Staff (Box 38)
        - Search Committee Nominations--Students (Box 38)
        - Search Process, 2 folders (Box 38)
        - Search Process Research (Box 38)
        - Timeline (Box 38)
        - Finalist Files, 4 folders (Box 38)
    - Public Health, School of
      - 1982-1984 (June Osborn)
        - Advertisement (Box 38)
        - Background and Information on the School of Public Health (Box 38)
        - Candidates (Box 38)
        - Correspondence (Box 38)
        - Evaluation of Candidates (Box 38)
        - Final Report to the Provost (Box 38)
        - Forms and Form Letters (Box 38)
        - Interview Questions (Box 38)
        - Position Description and Selection Criteria (Box 38)
        - Search Committee Agendas and Minutes (Box 38)
        - Search Committee Membership (Box 38)
        - Finalist Files, 8 folders (Box 38)
      - 1994-1995 (Noreen Clark)
        - Advertisement (Box 38)
        - Background Information on the School of Public Health (Box 38)
        - Candidates (Box 38)
        - Correspondence (Box 39)
        - Final Report to the Provost (Box 39)
        - Forms and Form Letters (Box 39)
        - Interim Dean (Box 39)
        - Interview Questions (Box 39)
        - Position Description and Selection Criteria (Box 39)
        - Provost's Poll of the Faculty on Issues (Box 39)
        - Provost's Report to the Regents (Box 39)
        - Redacted Documents (Box 39)
        - Search Committee Agendas and Minutes (Box 39)
        - Search Committee Membership (Box 39)
        - Timeline (Box 39)
        - Finalist Files, 3 folders (Box 39)
    - Public Policy, School of
      - 1997-1999 (Rebecca Blank)
        - Advertisement (Box 39)
        - Background Information on the School of Public Policy (Box 39)
        - Candidates (Box 39)
        - Correspondence (Box 39)
        - Final Report to the Provost (Box 39)
        - Forms and Form Letters (Box 39)
        - Interview Questions (Box 39)
        - Position Description and Selection Criteria (Box 39)
        - Search Committee Agendas and Minutes (Box 39)
        - Search Committee Membership (Box 39)
        - Search Committee's Poll of the Faculty on Issues (Box 39)
        - Search Consultants (Box 39)
        - Timeline (Box 39)
        - Finalist Files, 7 folders (Box 39)
    - Registrar
      - 1992 (Laura McCain Patterson)
        - Advertisement (Box 39)
        - Background Information on Registrar's Office (Box 39)
        - Candidates (Box 39)
        - Consultants' Visit (Box 39)
        - Correspondence (Box 40)
        - Forms and Form Letters (Box 40)
        - Position Description and Selection Criteria (Box 40)
        - Search Committee Agendas and Minutes (Box 40)
        - Search Committee Membership (Box 40)
        - Timeline (Box 40)
    - Secretary of the University
      - 1993-1995 (Roberta Palmer) (Box 40)
    - Social Work, School of
      - 1991-1992 (Paula Allen-Meares)
        - Advertisement (Box 40)
        - Background Information on the School of Social Work (Box 40)
        - Correspondence (Box 40)
        - Final Report to the Provost (Box 40)
        - Forms and Form Letters (Box 40)
        - Interview Questions (Box 40)
        - Open Meetings Act (Box 40)
        - Position Description and Selection Criteria (Box 40)
        - Provost's Poll of the Faculty on Key Issues (Box 40)
        - Provost's Report to the Regents (Box 40)
        - Search Committee Agendas and Minutes (Box 40)
        - Search Committee Membership (Box 40)
        - Finalist Files, 4 folders (Box 40)
    - University of Michigan-Flint, Chancellor
      - 1993-1994 (Charlie Nelms) (Box 40)
    - [Executive] Vice President and Chief Financial Officer
      - 1987-1988 (Farris Womack) (Box 40)
      - 1997 (Robert Kasdin) (Box 40)
    - Vice President and General Counsel
    - Vice President for Academic Affairs and Provost, Office of the
      - Provost
        - 1986 (James Duderstadt) (Box 40)
        - 1988 (Charles Vest) (Box 40)
        - 1995 (Bernie Machen) (Box 40)
      - Associate Vice President
        - 1989-1990 (Mary Ann Swain) (Box 40)
        - 1993 (Susan Lipschutz) (Box 40)
      - Senior Policy Advisor
        - 1994 (Box 40)
    - Vice President for Development and University Relations
      - 1993-1994) (Box 40)
    - Vice President for Research, Office of the
      - 1990 (William C. Kelly)
        - Background Information OVPR, 3 folders (Box 40)
        - Candidates (Box 40)
        - Correspondence (Box 40)
        - Final Report to the Provost (Box 40)
        - Notes (Box 40)
        - Position Description and Selection Criteria (Box 40)
        - President's Report to the Regents (Box 40)
        - Search Committee Membership (Box 40)
        - Kelly, William C. (Box 40)
      - 1998-1999 (Fawwaz Ulaby)
        - Advertisement (Box 40)
        - Background Information on OVPR, 2 folders (Box 40)
        - Candidates (Box 40)
        - Correspondence (Box 40)
        - Forms and Form Letters (Box 40)
        - Position Description and Selection Criteria (Box 40)
        - Provost's Poll of the Faculty on Key Issues for OVPR (Box 40)
        - Search Committee Agendas and Minutes (Box 40)
        - Search Consultants (Box 41)
        - Timeline (Box 41)